A Guide to the Records of the Public Library Development Division of the Virginia State Library and Archives, 1920-1992
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Director's correspondence and subject files, 1920-1992., Extent: 45.15 cubic feet (129 boxes). (Box 1-129)
  - Subject files, 1928-1989.
    - State aid, 1954. (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - State aid, 1954. (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - State aid, 1956. (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - State aid, 1957-1961. (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - State aid, 1961-1962. (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - State aid, 1962-1963. (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - State aid, 1963-1964. (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - State aid, 1964-1965. (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - State aid, 1965-1967. (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - State aid, 1967-1968. (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - State aid, 1968-1970. (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - State aid, 1973-1975. (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - State Library Board - Memoranda, 1946-1954. (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - State Library Board - Reports for Board meetings on libraries qualifiying for state aid, 1945-1955. (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - State Library Board - Reports for Board meetings on libraries qualifying for state aid, 1956-1965. (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - State and National Planning Committee, 1947-1950. (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - State plans, 1964-1966. (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Statistics - Virginia Library Service, 1941. (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Statistics - Virginia Libraries - General, 1943-1945. (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Statistics - Virginia Public Libraries, 1943. (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Supplies for Demonstration Libraries, 1959-1967. (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Survey of Public Library Building Facilities, 1965. (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Survey of Special Libraries serving State Government, 1964-1965. (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Surveys of Public Libraries, 1945-1952. (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Surveys of Public Libraries, 1954. (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Surveys of Public Libraries, 1960-1963. (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Tennessee Valley Library Council, 1941-1945. (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Tennessee Valley Library Council, 1946. (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Tennessee Valley Library Council, 1947. (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Tennessee Valley Library Council, 1948-1949. (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Tidewater Area - Northern, 1963. (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Tidewater Regional Library, 1941. (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Traveling Libraries, 1944. (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Traveling Libraries, 1944-1951. (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Traveling Libraries - Procedureds, 1948. (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Traveling Libraries - Monthly statistics (Record of Traveling Libraries sent out), 1949-1958. (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - University of Virginia, 1945-1951. (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - University of Virginia, 1952-1958. (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - University of Virginia, 1959-1963. (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Adult Education Association, 1950-1954. (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Adult Education Association, 1955-1957. (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Advisory Legislation Council, 1958-1969. (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Citizens Planning Association, 1951-1966. (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian (quarterly publication), 1970. (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian (quarterly publication), 1974. (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian (quarterly publication), 1975. (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian (quarterly publication), 1986. (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian (quarterly publication), 1987. (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian (quarterly publication), 1988. (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian (quarterly publication), 1989. (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian Newsletter, 1976. (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian Newsletter, 1977. (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian Newsletter, 1978. (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian Newsletter, 1979. (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian Newsletter, 1980. (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian Newsletter, 1981. (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian Newsletter, 1982. (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian Newsletter, 1983. (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian Newsletter, 1984. (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Library Association - Virginia Librarian Newsletter, 1985. (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Library Association Newsletter, 1987. (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Library Association Newsletter, 1988. (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Library Association Newsletter, 1989. (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1928-1930. (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1935. (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1936. (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1937-1938. (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1939-1940. (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1941-1943. (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1944-1945. (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1946. (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1947-1948. (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1949-1950. (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1951-1954. (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1955-1956. (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1957-1958. (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1959-1960. (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1961-1962. (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1963-1964. (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1965-1967. (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Library Association - Activities Committee, 1937. (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Library Association - Annual meeting (Danville), 1937. (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Library Association - Annual meeting, 1937. (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Library Association - Annual meeting, 1951. (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Library Association - Certification and salaries, 1937. (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Library Association - Citizens, 1935-1940. (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Library Association - Constitution Revision Committee, 1951. (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Library Association - Intellectual Freedom Committee, 1948-1950. (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Library Association - Junior members, 1936-1937. (Box 119, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Library Association - Legislative Committee, 1946-1950. (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Library Association - Legislative Committee, 1951-1953. (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Library Association - Library Development Committee, 1948-1949. (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Library Association - Library Development Committee, 1950. (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Library Association - Library Development Committee, 1950. (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Library Association - Library Development Committee, 1951-1952. (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Library Association - Library Protective Committee, 1937. (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Library Association - Membership and Finance Committee, 1937. (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Library Association - Membership, 1951-1958. (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Library Association - Programs, 1934-1936, 1941, 1947. (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Library Association - Regional Libraries, 1937. (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Library Association - School librarians, 1937. (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Library Association - State Aid, 1937. (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Library Association - Trustees, 1937. (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 1-3), 1937. (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 4), 1944. (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 5), 1944. (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 6), 1945. (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 7), 1946. (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 8), 1946. (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 9), 1947. (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 10), 1947. (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 11), 1948. (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 12), 1948. (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 13), 1949. (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 14-15), 1950. (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 16), 1951. (Box 121, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 17), 1951. (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 18), 1951. (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 19), 1952. (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin (No. 20), 1953. (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Library Bulletin - Correspondence and articles, 194301963. (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute - Extension Service, 1948-1956. (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Special Library Service, 1950-1954. (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - VISTA book kits, 1966-1967. (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1960. (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - William and Mary College, 1947-1967. (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Lonesome Pine Regional Library JLARC Study files, 1982-1990.
    This sub-series consists of 7 boxes and is arranged alphabetically.
    - Annual reports, 1982-1989. (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Articles on non-book materials, 1985-1990. (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Automation, 1987-1990. (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Books by mail, 1982-1989. (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Branches, undated. (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Brochures, 1985-1989. (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Circulation, 1982-1990. (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Circulation, 1982-1990. (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Circulation, 1982-1990. (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Circulation reports - Big Stone Gap, 1982-1989. (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Circulation reports - Clinchco, 1982-1984. (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Circulation reports - Coeburn, 1982-1989. (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Circulation reports - Dickenson, 1982-1989. (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Circulation reports - Haysi, 1982-1989. (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Circulation reports - Lee County, 1982-1989. (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Circulation reports - Rose Hill, 1982-1989. (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Circulation reports - Scott County, 1982-1989. (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Circulation reports - St. Paul, 1982-1989. (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Circulation reports - Wise County, 1982-1989. (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Circulation - Mailbox Library, 1982-1989. (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Circulation - Bookmobile, 1982 July-1983 June. (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Circulation - Bookmobile, 1983 July-1984 June. (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Circulation - Bookmobile, 1984 July-1985 June. (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Circulation - Bookmobile, 1985 July-1986 June. (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Circulation - Bookmobile, 1986 July-1987 June. (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Circulation - Bookmobile, 187 July-1988 June. (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 1964-1965. (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 1967. (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Clippings, 1968-1969. (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Clippings, 1970-1971. (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Clippings, 1972. (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Clippings, 1973. (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Clippings, 1974. (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Clippings, 1975. (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1976-1977. (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1978-1979. (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1980-1981. (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1982-1985. (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Clippings, 1989. (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, undated. (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Corrections, 1983-1989. (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1990. (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Definitions, undated. (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Drafts, 1989-1990. (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Finance, 1990. (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Issues, undated. (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - Lee County, 1981. (Box 126, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, undated. (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Notes, undated. (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Performance measures, undated. (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Personnel, 1988. (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Policy Manual, 1989-1990. (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Profiles, 1990. (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Profiles, 1990. (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Publicity, 1990. (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Questionnaires, 1990. (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Recommendations, undated. (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Statistics, 1989-1990. (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - JLARC Special Report on the Lonesome Pine Regional Library System, 1990 Sept. (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Progress report and letter in response to the JLARC report and appendices, 1992. (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Report Appendix A: New Personnel Manual, 1992. (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Report Appendix B: Retrospective Conversion Project Information, 1992. (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Report Appendix C: Position Description and Performance Planning and Evaluation forms, 1992. (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Report Appendix D: Performance Evaluation Assignments, 1992. (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Report Appendix E: Open Position Information, 1992. (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Report Appendix F: Training Details, 1992. (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Report Appendix G: Public Service Policy, 1992. (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Report Appendix H: Sample Position Description and Performance and Evaluation forms, 1992. (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Report Appendix I: Board Member Manual, 1991. (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Report Appendix J: Director's Visitation Schedule, 1991-1992. (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - Report Appendix K: Circulation Statistics, 1992 Aug. (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Report Appendix L: Lease Agreements, 1991. (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Report Appendix M: Budget Documentation, 1992. (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Report Appendix N: Procurement Information / Budget Requests, 1992. (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - Report Appendix N: Audit, 1992. (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Report Appendix O: Library hours / Revised schedule, 1992. (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Report Appendix P: Library calendars - Brochures, 1992. (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Report Appendix Q: Circulation statistics, 1992. (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Report Appendix R: Miscellaneous publicity materials, 1992. (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Report Appendix R: Miscellaneous publicity materials - Wise County Public Library and branches, 1992. (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Report Appendix R: Miscellaneous publicity materials - C. Bascom Stemp Memorial Library, 1992. (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Report Appendix R: Miscellaneous publicity materials - J. Fred Mathews Memorial Library (St. Paul), 1992. (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Report Appendix R: Miscellaneous publicity materials - Jonnie B. Deel Memorial Library, 1992. (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Report Appendix R: Miscellaneous publicity materials - Haysi Public Library, 1992. (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Report Appendix R: Miscellaneous publicity materials - Lee County Public Library, 1992. (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Report Appendix R: Miscellaneous publicity materials - Scott County Public Library, 1992. (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Report Appendix S: Reference information, 1992. (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Report Appendix T: Database brochure, 1992. (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Report Appendix U: Mailbox booklets, 1992. (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Report Appendix V: Five Year Plan, 1992. (Box 129, Folder 15)
- Series II. Library Consultant files, 1968-1987., Extent: 13.65 cubic feet (39 boxes). (Box 130-168)
  Library Consultant files, 1968-1987, are housed in 39 boxes and are arranged alphabetically. These files are divided into the four consultive regions (Areas I-IV) and contain general correspondence and subject files, consultant's correspondence with the various libraries in their region, meeting notes and reports.
  - Area I files, 1968-1987.
    XX
    - General correspondence (Public Libraries), 1987. (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence (Public Libraries), 1986. (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence (Public Libraries), 1985. (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence (Public Libraries), 1984. (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - General correspondence (Public Libraries), 1983. (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - General correspondence (Public Libraries), 1982. (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - General correspondence (Public Libraries), 1981. (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - General correspondence (Public Libraries), 1980. (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - General correspondence (Public Libraries), 1979. (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - General correspondence (Public Libraries), 1973. (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - General records, 1971-1985. (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - General correspondence (Virginia State Library), 1987. (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - General correspondence (Virginia State Library), 1986. (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - General correspondence (Virginia State Library), 1985. (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - General correspondence (Virginia State Library), 1984. (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence (Virginia State Library), 1983. (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence (Virginia State Library), 1982. (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence (Virginia State Library), 1981. (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - General correspondence (Virginia State Library), 1980. (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - General correspondence (Virginia State Library), 1979. (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - General correspondence (Virginia State Library), 1978. (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - General correspondence (Virginia State Library), 1977. (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - General correspondence (Virginia State Library), 1971-1976. (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Deaf, Blind and Physically Handicapped Workshop, 1976. (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Film Services, 1979-1982. (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Library Services and Construction Act (Title I) - Basic grants, 1982-1985. (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Library Services and Construction Act (Title I) - Federal aid, 1976-1985. (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Library Services and Construction Act (Title I) - Special Purpose Applications, 1966-1982. (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Library Services and Construction Act (Title I) - Special Purpose Grants - Proposals, 1974-1975. (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Library Services and Construction Act (Title I) - Special Purpose Grants - Rules and Regulations, 1970-1980. (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Library Services and Construction Act (Title II), 1983-1985. (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Library Services and Construction Act (Title III), 1976-1986. (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Minimum standards, undated. (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Personnel, 1975-1986. (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Personnel - Job descriptions, 1985-1986. (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Reports - Annual, 1971-1986. (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1971. (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1972. (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1973. (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1974. (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1975. (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1976. (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1977. (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1978. (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1979. (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1980. (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1981. (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1982. (Box 133, Folder 16)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1983. (Box 133, Folder 17)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1984. (Box 133, Folder 18)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1985. (Box 133, Folder 19)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1986. (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Reports - Quarterly, 1987. (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Revenue Sharing, 1973-1974. (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Special Purpose Grants, 1981-1983. (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1984-1987. (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1978-1983. (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Library Association, 1972-1978. (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Western Region Consortium on Continuing Higher Education, 1977. (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - White House Conference on Libraries and Information Science, 1977. (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - White House Conference on Libraries and Information Science, 1978. (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - White House Conference on Libraries and Information Science, 1978. (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - White House Conference on Libraries and Information Science, 1979. (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - White House Conference on Libraries and Information Science, 1979. (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - White House Conference on Libraries and Information Science, 1981. (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Blue Ridge Regional Library, 1980-1987. (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Blue Ridge Regional Library, 1970-1979. (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Botetourt County Library, 1981-1986. (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Botetourt County Library, 1977-1980. (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Bristol Public Library, 1971-1986. (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Carroll County Public Library, 1981-1982. (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Carroll County Public Library, 1971-1980. (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Clifton Forge Public Library, 1971-87. (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Charles P. Jones Memorial Library, 1981-1987. (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Charles P. Jones Memorial Library, 1971-1980. (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Danville Public Library, 1971-1986. (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Franklin County Library, 1975-1986. (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Franklin - Patrick Regional Library, 1971-1975. (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Galax - Carroll Regional Library, 1977-1987. (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Galax - Carroll Regional Library, 1971-1976. (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Giles County, 1974-1978. (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Henry County, 1971-1975. (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library, 1981-1987. (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library, 1971-1980. (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Martinsville - Henry Regional Library, 1975. (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Martinsville - Henry Regional Library, 1974. (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Martinsville - Henry Regional Library, 1972-1973. (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Martinsville Memorial Library, 1972. (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Martinsville Memorial Library, 1971. (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Montgomery - Floyd Regional Library, 1985-1987. (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Montgomery - Floyd Regional Library, 1982-1984. (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Montgomery - Floyd Regional Library, 1979-1981. (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Montgomery - Floyd Regional Library, 1976-1978. (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Montgomery - Floyd Regional Library, 1971-1975. (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Montgomery - Floyd Regional Library - Blacksburg Branch, 1970-1984. (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Montgomery - Floyd Regional Library - Building, 1984-1986. (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Montgomery - Floyd Regional Library - Building, 192. (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Mount Rogers Regional Library, 1972-1978. (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Narrows Public Library, 1972-1986. (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - New River Regional Library, undated. (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Pearisburg Public Library, 1985-1987. (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Pearisburg Public Library, 1983-1984. (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Pearisburg Public Library, 1980-1981. (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Pearisburg Public Library, 1977-1978. (Box 139, Folder 7)